You're paying me to work, not to be spoken to like that!
أنت تدفع لي مقابل العمل، لا يجوز التحدث بهذه الطريقة!
You're so harsh!
أنت قاسٍ جدًا!
[SCREAMS]
[صراخ]
I really don't know why Martin hired you as a secretary.
أنا حقا لا أعرف لماذا مارتن عينتك سكرتيرة.
You're the total opposite of him.
أنت عكسه تمامًا.
Well, opposites attract, right?
حسنًا، الأضداد تتجاذب، أليس كذلك؟
- You're the hotel owners. - Mm.
- أنتم أصحاب الفندق. - مم.
And he's a partner, so you're on the same level.
وهو شريك، إذن أنتم على نفس المستوى.
Handsome, rich,
وسيم، غني،
and business-minded!
وذو عقلية تجارية!
You feel insecure?
هل تشعر بعدم الأمان؟
This is him, and this is me. There's a huge gap!
هذا هو، وهذا أنا. هناك فجوة كبيرة!
I think you should finish what you started.
أعتقد أنه يجب عليك الانتهاء ما بدأته.
Don't leave her hanging.
لا تتركها معلقة.
Kiko, are you alright?
كيكو، هل أنت بخير؟
I just have so much work to do.
لدي الكثير من العمل للقيام به.
I don't want the new investor to think
لا أريد المستثمر الجديد الذي يجب أن يفكر
that our workers are lazy.
أن عمالنا كسالى.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى هادئة]
[CLEARS THROAT] Miss Jade.
[ينظف الحلق] الآنسة جايد.
Don't you think you're staring a bit too much?
لا تظن كنت يحدق قليلا أكثر من اللازم؟
Me?
أنا؟
You?
أنت؟
Well, there's no one else here.
حسنًا، لا يوجد أحد آخر هنا.
Come here. Let's have a talk.
تعال الى هنا. دعونا نتحدث.
- Ow... - Sit here.
- اه... - اجلس هنا.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل الموسيقى]
[THEME MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى]
So, what's the deal with you and Sir Kiko?
إذن، ما هي الصفقة معك والسيد كيكو؟
Why do people keep asking me that?
لماذا الناس استمر في سؤالي عن ذلك؟
Oh, do they?
أوه، هل هم؟
Then, other people can see what I've been seeing.
وبعد ذلك، يمكن للآخرين أن يروا ما كنت أرى.
- What? - That you're not just friends.
- ماذا؟ - أنك لست مجرد أصدقاء.
Raphie, we're just friends.
رافي، نحن مجرد أصدقاء.
That's not what I'm seeing.
هذا ليس ما أراه.
I'm not sure if I'm the only one,
لست متأكدا إذا كنت الوحيد،
but from the moment you came back here,
ولكن من لحظة لقد عدت إلى هنا،
he's always been present in your life.
لقد كان دائما حاضر في حياتك.
You were together for the Roi incident.
كنتما معًا لحادثة روي.
[GASPS]
[لهث]
Kiko!
كيكو!
Jade?
اليشم؟
- Jade! Jade! - [SOBBING]
-اليشم! يشم! - [ينتحب]
- What's wrong? - Kiko...
- ما هو الخطأ؟ - كيكو...
And then, during the team-building...
وبعد ذلك، أثناء بناء الفريق...
Jade.
اليشم.
- I got it. - No, it's okay.
-لقد حصلت عليه. - لا، لا بأس.
- It's okay, I got it. - It's fine...
- لا بأس، فهمت. - لا بأس...
- Mudcart! - Yes!
- عربة الطين! - نعم!
I'll carry you.
سأحملك.
- Kiko, I'm fine. - Jade.
- كيكو، أنا بخير. - اليشم.
You're hurt. I'll carry you.
كنت يصب بأذى. سأحملك.
Just go ahead.
تفضل فقط.
I'm not going to leave you here.
أنا لن أذهب لأتركك هنا.
Come on.
هيا.
[GRUNTS]
[الهمهمات]
[RAPHIE] And...
[رافي] و...
I think you were also together
أعتقد أنكما كنتما معًا أيضًا
when you were gone these past few days.
عندما ذهبت هذه الأيام القليلة الماضية.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS]
[عزف موسيقى لطيف]
[RAPHIE] Am I right, Miss Jade?
[رافي] هل أنا على حق، يا آنسة جايد؟
[CHUCKLES]
[ضحكة مكتومة]
Is that wrong?
هل هذا خطأ؟
Of course, not.
بالطبع لا.
But it also isn't normal for "just friends."
لكنه ليس طبيعيا أيضا من أجل "الأصدقاء فقط".
You guys have something.
يا رفاق لديك شيء.
I can feel it.
أستطيع أن أشعر به.
I can feel it in my fingers, in my hair...
أستطيع أن أشعر به في أصابعي، في شعري...
in your heart.
في قلبك.
[TEASES]
[إغاظة]
In my... heart?
في قلبي...؟
Yeah!
نعم!
I don't know, but...
لا أعلم ولكن...
I feel like he's avoiding me these past few days.
أشعر وكأنه يتجنبني هذه الأيام القليلة الماضية.
[JADE] I don't know what I did wrong.
[اليشم] لا أعرف ما الخطأ الذي فعلته.
Have you asked him?
هل سألته؟
No.
رقم
It just doesn't make sense.
هذا لا معنى له.
Sometimes, he's so sweet and kind to me.
في بعض الأحيان، يكون لطيفًا جدًا ولطيف معي.
I don't know what his actions mean.
لا أعرف ماذا تعني أفعاله.
When something's confusing, clear it up!
عندما يكون هناك شيء مربك، امسحها!
We don't have time for mixed signals anymore.
ليس لدينا الوقت للإشارات المختلطة بعد الآن.
Yeah.
نعم.
Yeah, you're right.
نعم، أنت على حق.
- If it's confusing... - Mm-hm.
- إذا كان الأمر محيراً.. - مم هم.
- I should clear it up. - Yes!
- يجب أن أوضح الأمر. - نعم!
That's my girly pop.
هذا هو البوب ​​جرلي الخاص بي.
So, if he can't say what he really feels,
لذلك، إذا كان لا يستطيع أن يقول ما يشعر به حقًا،
I'll say mine.
سأقول الألغام.
Perfect!
ممتاز!
That's perfect!
هذا ممتاز!
Do that, Miss Jade!
افعلي ذلك يا آنسة جايد!
I'll root for you.
سوف الجذر بالنسبة لك.
You're being too much.
أنت تبالغ.
[CHUCKLES] Oh. Sorry.
[ضحكة مكتومة] أوه. آسف.
That's the problem when you're too bored.
هذه هي المشكلة عندما تشعر بالملل الشديد.
You keep following me around.
أنت تواصل متابعتي في كل مكان.
Kiko, I just want an update about you and Jade.
كيكو، أريد فقط التحديث عنك وعن اليشم.
Come on.
تعال.
Just help me with this, will you?
فقط ساعدني في هذا، هل ستفعل؟
- Here. Thank you. - You know what?
- هنا. شكرًا لك. - أتعلم؟
You shouldn't even be doing this.
لا ينبغي لك حتى أن تفعل هذا.
This is your employees' job.
هذه هي وظيفة موظفيك.
You're the real bored one here.
أنت الملل الحقيقي هنا.
So, what's up with you and Jade?
إذن، ما الأمر معك و اليشم؟
Hey, spill the tea!
مهلا، صب الشاي!
I don't have to update you about anything.
ليس من الضروري أن أقوم بتحديثك عن أي شيء.
Jade and I are just friends.
جايد وأنا مجرد أصدقاء.
[CHESKA SCOFFS] Friends?
[تشيسكا يسخر] أصدقاء؟
You're such a prude.
أنت مثل هذا فخور.
Hey! Those are clean sheets!
يا! تلك أوراق نظيفة!
I don't care. I'll clean you up.
لا أهتم. سأقوم بتنظيفك.
I'll clean your brain up.
سأقوم بتنظيف دماغك.
The last time we talked, you said, "soon."
آخر مرة تحدثنا فيها، قلت: "قريبا".
You said you needed a good timing.
قلت أنك بحاجة توقيت جيد.
So, what now?
فماذا الآن؟
I realized I don't need it anymore.
أدركت أنني لا أحتاج إليها بعد الآن.
What?
ماذا؟
[EXHALES] What does that mean?
[زفير] ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Jade and I are just friends.
جايد وأنا مجرد أصدقاء.
I only see her as a friend.
أنا أراها فقط كصديقة.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
[تشغيلات موسيقية حزينة]
Alright, Pinocchio.
حسنًا يا بينوكيو.
Why am I even your sister
لماذا أنا أختك أصلا
if I don't know how you really feel?
إذا كنت لا أعرف كيف تشعر حقا؟
We're just so different.
نحن مختلفون تمامًا.
She lives lavishly, and I'm from the streets.
وهي تعيش ببذخ، وأنا من الشوارع.
[SCOFFS] What is this, a drama?
[سكوفس] ما هذه الدراما؟
"We're worlds apart, so we can't be together."
"نحن عالمان متباعدان، لذلك لا يمكننا أن نكون معًا."
My god.
يا إلاهي.
I know she's not that kind of person.
أعلم أنها ليست كذلك هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
We just have very different interests
لدينا فقط اهتمامات مختلفة جدًا
and priorities in life.
والأولويات في الحياة.
Plus, Edward...
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، إدوارد...
What? That she's more compatible with Edward
ماذا؟ أنها أكثر متوافق مع إدوارد
because he's as rich as she is?
لأنه غني مثلها؟
When they're together, it feels special.
عندما يكونان معًا، إنه شعور خاص.
Special?
خاص؟
Why? Are they steamed buns?
لماذا؟ هل هم الكعك على البخار؟
Do they have a red dot on their heads?
هل لديهم نقطة حمراء على رؤوسهم؟
What's so special about them?
ما الذي يميزهم؟
All I'm saying is, I can't compete with that.
كل ما أقوله هو، لا أستطيع التنافس مع ذلك.
How can I ever beat Edward?
كيف يمكنني التغلب على إدوارد؟
- Just look at me. - You look dirty!
- فقط أنظر إلي. - أنت تبدو قذرة!
I mean, those stuff look dirty.
أعني أن تلك الأشياء تبدو قذرة.
[CHUCKLES]
[ضحكة مكتومة]
I don't know if she noticed, but I've been avoiding her.
لا أعرف إذا كانت قد لاحظت، لكنني كنت أتجنبها.
What?!
ماذا؟!
Why did you do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
- I'm crazy, I know. - Yes, you are!
- أنا مجنون، وأنا أعلم. - نعم أنت على حق!
I know. And I know it was wrong.
أنا أعرف. وأنا أعلم أنه كان خطأ.
I shouldn't have done that.
لا ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك.
Well...
حسنا...
But you did do it.
ولكنك فعلت ذلك.
You have to make it up to her.
عليك أن تجعل الأمر لها.
Go talk to her.
اذهب وتحدث معها.
And don't let your insecurities get the best of you.
ولا تدع عدم الأمان الخاص بك احصل على أفضل ما لديك.
That's not right.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
You can't just forget about your feelings because of that.
لا يمكنك أن تنسى الأمر فحسب مشاعرك بسبب ذلك.
Come on, man.
هيا يا رجل.
I'm... I'm just trying to be practical.
أنا... أنا فقط تحاول أن تكون عملية.
I don't want to push it too far that it becomes awkward.
لا أريد أن أدفع الأمر بعيدًا أنه يصبح محرجا.
I'm fine with what we've got.
أنا بخير مع ما لدينا.
I'm just glad to have her in my life again.
أنا سعيد فقط أن يكون لها في حياتي مرة أخرى.
I don't want to ruin our friendship with my feelings.
أنا لا أريد أن تدمر لدينا الصداقة مع مشاعري.
[SIGHS] Suit yourself.
[تنهدات] تناسب نفسك.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الهادئة]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى حزينة]
[SOBBING, SNIFFLING]]
[ تنتحب، تشهق ]]
Why are you crying, Jade?
لماذا تبكي يا جايد؟
Why are you hurting?
لماذا تتألم؟
There's nothing you can do,
لا يوجد شيء يمكنك القيام به،
Kiko only sees you as a friend!
كيكو يراك فقط كصديق!
See?
يرى؟
See?!
يرى؟!
It's because you keep thinking about so many things.
هذا لأنك تحافظ عليه التفكير في أشياء كثيرة.
Turns out he only sees you as a friend.
اتضح أنه لا يراك إلا أنت كصديق.
It's all your fault!
كل هذا خطأك!
It's all your fault for expecting something!
كل هذا خطأك لتوقع شيء ما!
Jade?
يشم؟
[JADE CONTINUES SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
[يستمر اليشم في النحيب، الشهقة ]
Something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما ؟
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الحزينة]
[EDWARD GROANS]
[إدوارد جرونز]
Here.
هنا.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Just use my shoulder to weep your tears with.
مجرد استخدام كتفي لتبكي دموعك معها.
Seriously?
بجد؟
Using your clothes?
باستخدام ملابسك؟
Yeah well, I don't have a handkerchief with me.
نعم حسنا، ليس لدي منديل معي.
This shirt is pretty expensive, you know?
هذا القميص غالي الثمن جداً هل تعلم؟
But I can always buy a new one.
لكن يمكنني دائمًا شراء واحدة جديدة.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الحزينة]
[CHESKA] You're not even hiding
[تشيسكا] أنت لا تختبئ حتى
how you're waiting for Justin anymore, huh?
كيف تنتظر لجوستين بعد الآن، هاه؟
Because I'm starting to feel impatient.
لأنني بدأت أن تشعر بفارغ الصبر.
I already want to start the bar business.
أريد بالفعل أن أبدأ أعمال الحانة.
I already made a business plan and everything.
لقد قمت بالفعل بوضع خطة عمل وكل شيء.
The only thing missing is the bar itself.
الشيء الوحيد المفقود هو الشريط نفسه.
So you already made a lot of progress, huh.
لذلك قمت بالفعل الكثير من التقدم، هاه.
But not with apologizing, I guess.
ولكن ليس مع الاعتذار أعتقد.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى حزينة]
Alright. Let's say that apologizing
على ما يرام. دعنا نقول أن الاعتذار
wasn't really in your plan in the first place.
لم يكن حقا في خطتك في المقام الأول.
Well, it already seems so impossible.
حسنا، يبدو بالفعل مستحيل جدا.
It's not like you'll be seeing him again, right?
ليس الأمر كما لو كنت رؤيته مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
He got suspended by Luna after all.
لقد تم ايقافه عن العمل بواسطة لونا بعد كل شيء.
You mean he's never going back here at all?!
تقصد أنه لم يفعل ذلك أبداً العودة هنا على الإطلاق؟!
No way, Cheska! I have to talk to him!
مستحيل يا تشيسكا! لا بد لي من التحدث معه!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى لطيف]
What if we visit his house?
ماذا لو قمنا بزيارة منزله؟
You know where he lives?
هل تعرف أين يعيش؟
Nope.
لا.
But we can ask Jade and Luna, right?
ولكن يمكننا أن نسأل اليشم ولونا، أليس كذلك؟
We can.
نستطيع.
[CHESKA CHUCKLES]
[ضحكات شيسكا]
Won't he be shocked with us suddenly
لن يكون بالصدمة معنا فجأة
showing up at his doorstep?
تظهر على عتبة بابه؟
What if...
ماذا لو...
you give him a call first?
هل اتصلت به أولاً؟
Alright, go do it then.
حسنًا، اذهب وافعل ذلك بعد ذلك.
The hell...
الجحيم...
My idea, my work.
فكرتي وعملي.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[اهتزاز الهاتف]
Justin, my friend!
جاستن، صديقي!
- [JUSTIN] Hello? - Yeah!
- [جوستين] ​​مرحبًا؟ - نعم!
It's been a while since you last visited the hotel!
لقد مضى وقت طويل منذ ذلك الحين آخر مرة زرت الفندق!
How's it going?
كيف الحال؟
[JUSTIN] I have some business to attend to.
[جوستين] لدي البعض الأعمال التي يتعين عليك حضورها.
Huh?
هاه؟
Well, that's new! You busy?
حسنا، هذا جديد! أأنت مشغول؟
What?
ماذا؟
Let's go get some drinks!
دعنا نذهب للحصول على بعض المشروبات!
[JUSTIN] Alright, alright. I'll send you a message.
[جوستين] ​​حسنًا، حسنًا. سأرسل لك رسالة.
Yeah, message me the time and place.
نعم، أرسل لي رسالة الزمان والمكان.
Later then!
في وقت لاحق بعد ذلك!
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Bye, my friend!
وداعا يا صديقي!
[JUSTIN] Bye-bye.
[جوستين] وداعا.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[صفير الهاتف]
All done. We'll meet him later.
تم كل شيء. سنلتقي به لاحقا.
[SIGHS] Okay.
[تنهدات] حسنا.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
[تشغيل موسيقى لطيف، يتلاشى]
You okay now?
هل أنت بخير الآن؟
Are you really not gonna tell me what happened?
هل أنت حقا لا هل ستخبرني ماذا حدث؟
["PANGHABANG IKAW" BY DARREN ESPANTO PLAYING]
["بانجابانج إيكاو" بقلم دارين لعب اسبانتو]
Okay, then. Let's consider this as a coffee update.
حسنًا إذن. دعونا نفكر في هذا كتحديث القهوة.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Just pay it no mind.
فقط ادفعها ولا مانع.
I would like to use my third wish right now.
أود أن استخدام أمنيتي الثالثة الآن.
Is it another breakfast?
هل هو فطور آخر؟
Because I'm telling you right now,
لأنني أقول لك الآن،
if it's breakfast, I won't be able to--
إذا كان الإفطار، لن أتمكن من--
I want you to be free.
أريدك أن تكون حرا.
So you're going to run away with me.
لذلك أنت ذاهب ليهرب معي.
What?
ماذا؟
Let's run away.
دعونا نركض بعيداً.
Somewhere far away so you won't have
في مكان بعيد لذلك لن يكون لديك
to worry about a thing.
للقلق بشأن شيء ما.
A vacation?
اجازة؟
If that's what you want,
إذا كان هذا ما تريد،
then yes,
فنعم
a vacation.
اجازة.
To get rid of that negative energy
للتخلص من تلك الطاقة السلبية
that's making you cry.
هذا يجعلك تبكي.
Hold up, you can't say no.
انتظر، لا يمكنك أن تقول لا.
I saved your life, remember?
لقد أنقذت حياتك، أتذكرين؟
When are we leaving?
متى سنغادر؟
[EDWARD CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
[إدوارد يضحك بخفة]
[EDWARD GRUNTING]
[إدوارد جرونتنج]
Let's get going.
دعونا نبدأ.
Let's go?
دعنا نذهب؟
["PANGHABANG IKAW" CONTINUES PLAYING]
["بانجابانج إيكاو" يتابع اللعب]
[EDWARD GROANING]
[إدوارد جراونينج]
[RAPHIE] I approved Room 201's request for a late checkout
[رافي] لقد وافقت على الغرفة 201 طلب تسجيل خروج متأخر
tomorrow because no one is booked in that room
غدا لأنه لا أحد تم حجزه في تلك الغرفة
- however, - Okay.
- ومع ذلك، - حسنا.
Room 206 asked for an extension.
سألت الغرفة 206 لتمديد.
206?
206؟
Hmm.
همم.
[WATER SPLASHING]
[رش الماء]
Sir?
سيد؟
Looks like the guest really took a liking to Sari!
يبدو مثل الضيف حقا أحب ساري!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[الأحاديث المتداخلة]
Thank you, Raphie. You can now go back to work.
شكرا لك، رافي. يمكنك الآن العودة إلى العمل.
Okay, sir.
حسنًا يا سيدي.
- [GUEST] Just us two! - [SARI LAUGHING] Sir!
- [ضيف] نحن الاثنان فقط! - [ساري يضحك] سيدي!
[GUEST] There's no one here! Come on!
[ضيف] لا يوجد أحد هنا! تعال!
[SARI] Go ahead, sir! I'm still working.
[ساري] تفضل يا سيدي! ما زلت أعمل.
[GUEST] It's so lonely here. Just join me!
[ضيف] الجو وحيد جدًا هنا. فقط انضم لي!
[SARI LAUGHING]
[ساري يضحك]
Sir?
سيد؟
Sir!
سيد!
[SARI GROANS] Sir!
[آهات ساري] سيدي!
Are you seriously doing that with our guest?
هل تفعل ذلك بجدية مع ضيفنا؟
- Sir?! - Don't sir me!
- سيد؟! - لا سيدي لي!
[PUFFS] I saw everything!
[نفث] رأيت كل شيء!
The way you laugh, the way you smile at him!
الطريقة التي تضحك بها، الطريقة التي تبتسم له!
- Sir, I didn't mean to! - "Didn't mean to!"
- سيدي، لم أقصد ذلك! - "لم أقصد!"
Really?
حقًا؟
You expect me to believe that?
هل تتوقع مني أن أصدق ذلك؟
Sari, it's so obvious to me
ساري، الأمر واضح جدًا بالنسبة لي
that you're flirting with a guest!
أنك تغازل مع ضيف!
[MARTIN SCOFFS] I don't care
[مارتن يسخر] أنا لا أهتم
if you're doing or if you're like this outside
إذا كنت تفعل أو إذا كنت مثل هذا بالخارج
but don't bring that behavior inside the hotel.
ولكن لا تجلب هذا السلوك داخل الفندق.
Because our hotel is not that kind of place.
لأن فندقنا ليس هذا النوع من المكان.
[SOBS] Aren't you too cruel?
[تنهدات] ألست قاسية للغاية؟
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى موروس]
Calling me a prostitute would've hurt less.
يدعوني عاهرة لقد كان سيؤذي أقل.
[SARI SOBBING]
[ساري ينتحب]
Why do I even bother asking you?
لماذا أنا حتى عناء يسألك؟
You should've talked to me properly about it first
كان يجب أن تتحدث معي بشكل صحيح حول هذا الموضوع أولا
before judging me.
قبل الحكم علي.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر موسيقى موروس]
Mmh. [THUDS]
مممم. [الصوت]
It's a peace offering.
إنها عرض السلام.
Sorry.
آسف.
What's that, Trixie?
ما هذا يا تريكسي؟
What kind of apology is that?
أي نوع من الاعتذار هو ذلك؟
I can really feel the sincerity in your voice!
أستطيع أن أشعر حقا بالصدق في صوتك!
That apology is colder than the drink you're about to have.
هذا الاعتذار أبرد من المشروب الذي أنت على وشك تناوله.
Fix it!
اصلاحه!
Cheska, an apology is an apology.
تشيسكا، اعتذار هو اعتذار.
What more do you want?
ماذا تريد أكثر من ذلك؟
There you go again.
ها أنت ذا مرة أخرى.
When you apologize,
عندما تعتذر
you should show that you're really sorry.
يجب أن تظهر أنك آسف حقا.
It should be felt in your voice.
يجب أن يشعر في صوتك.
Like this.
مثله.
Watch, okay?
شاهد، حسنًا؟
Justin, I'm sorry.
جاستن، أنا آسف.
I really didn't mean what I said.
أنا حقا لم أقصد ما قلته.
Like that! You can do it!
مثل ذلك! يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك!
Like that? Really?
مثل هذا؟ حقًا؟
You sound like you're trying too hard.
يبدو أنك تحاول صعب للغاية.
Look at you.
أنظر إليك.
We're practicing, and you're acting like that.
نحن نتدرب، وأنت تتصرف هكذا.
You don't take me seriously, and you keep contradicting me.
أنت لا تأخذني على محمل الجد، وتظل تناقضني.
- Come on! - Alright, fine.
- تعال! - حسنًا، حسنًا.
Cheska!
تشيسكا!
You didn't tell me you were with someone.
أنت لم تخبرني أنك كذلك مع شخص ما.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى متوترة]
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm blessing the house so your silence goes away.
أنا أبارك المنزل فيذهب صمتك.
You've been quiet at me for a while now.
لقد كنت هادئا في وجهي لفترة من الوقت الآن.
I got scolded by Sir Martin.
لقد وبخني السير مارتن.
He said some things to me.
قال لي بعض الأشياء.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى هادئة]
Are you sad because...
هل أنت حزين لأن...
you got scolded, or because of what he said to you?
لقد تم توبيخك، أو بسبب عما قاله لك؟
All of it.
كل ذلك.
Even if I was wrong,
ولو كنت مخطئا
I don't think I deserved to be spoken to like that,
لا أعتقد أنني أستحق أن يتم التحدث إليه بهذه الطريقة،
even if it came from someone perfect.
حتى لو جاءت من شخص مثالي.
Stop.
قف.
He's not perfect.
انه ليس مثاليا.
My granddaughter is the only one
حفيدتي هو الوحيد
who's close to perfect.
من هو قريب من الكمال.
- [CHUCKLES] - Grandpa, come on.
- [ضحكة مكتومة] - الجد، هيا.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
Even if what he said isn't true,
حتى لو كان ما قاله غير صحيح،
you're still sad because it came from someone you like.
كنت لا تزال حزينا لأنه جاءت من شخص تحبه
[SARI SIGHS]
[تنهدات ساري]
- Grandpa? - Hmm?
- الجد؟ - همم؟
What if the universe's sign is wrong?
ماذا لو كانت علامة الكون هو الخطأ؟
What if I was the only one who gave meaning to it,
ماذا لو كنت الوحيد من أعطى معناها،
that Sir Martin is really my soulmate?
أن السير مارتن هو حقا توأم روحي؟
What if he's not?
ماذا لو لم يكن كذلك؟
Do you like him because of the signs,
هل تحبه بسبب العلامات
or because of who he is?
أو بسبب من هو؟
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الناعمة]
[SARI SIGHS]
[تنهدات ساري]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى لطيف]
Miss! Miss!
يفتقد! يفتقد!
I don't think she can hear me.
لا أعتقد أنها تستطيع سماعي.
I'll just order some snacks.
سأطلب فقط بعض الوجبات الخفيفة.
- Do you want to eat? - I'll do it.
- هل تريد أن تأكل؟ - سأفعل ذلك.
I'll buy the snacks.
سأشتري الوجبات الخفيفة.
I'll get fries, nachos, and sea bass.
سأحضر البطاطس المقلية والناتشوز وباس البحر.
Sea bass? As a snack?
سمك باس البحر؟ كوجبة خفيفة؟
Uh, yeah.
اه نعم.
Sea bass is hard to find, though.
من الصعب العثور على باس البحر، رغم ذلك.
It might take a while.
قد يستغرق الأمر بعض الوقت.
I'll leave you two here.
سأترككما هنا.
I've got this.
لقد حصلت على هذا.
[AWKWARD GIGGLE]
[ضحكة محرجة]
[TRIXIE CLEARS THROAT]
[تريكسي ينظف الحلق]
[EXHALES]
[زفير]
I'm sorry I can't stay any longer, Grandma.
أنا آسف لأنني لا أستطيع البقاء بعد الآن يا جدتي.
I need to get back to the hotel
انا بحاجة للعودة إلى الفندق
so I can help my brothers.
حتى أتمكن من مساعدة إخوتي.
Last month, you were busy with a client.
الشهر الماضي، كنت مشغولاً مع العميل.
Now, it's your brothers.
الآن، هم إخوانك.
To be honest, they can manage without me.
لنكون صادقين، يمكنهم تدبر أمرهم بدوني.
But I still want to help them.
ولكن ما زلت أريد مساعدتهم.
I also have to take care of something at the hotel.
أنا أيضا يجب أن أعتني لشيء ما في الفندق.
Tell me the truth.
قل لي الحقيقة.
It has something to do with Luna, doesn't it?
لديها شيء لتفعله مع لونا، أليس كذلك؟
I guess so.
اعتقد ذلك.
I need to find out what she was doing
انا بحاجة لمعرفة ذلك ماذا كانت تفعل
while she was here in Manila.
بينما كانت هنا في مانيلا.
[SIGHS]
[تنهدات]
Oh, okay.
أوه، حسنا.
If this is about you and Luna, go ahead.
إذا كان هذا حول أنت ولونا، تفضلا.
You're a brave kid.
أنت طفل شجاع.
So...
إذن...
Go face this.
اذهب وواجه هذا.
Thank you, Grandma.
شكرا لك يا جدتي.
- Mm. - Mwah!
- مم. - مواه!
Always take care, my dear.
كن حذرا دائما يا عزيزي.
Yes, Grandma.
نعم الجدة.
- Mm... - I'll go ahead now.
- مم... - سأمضي قدما الآن.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى متأمل]
Our lawyers are already drafting the agreement.
محامونا موجودون بالفعل صياغة الاتفاقية.
Good, good.
جيد، جيد.
Michael's children also agreed to partner with me.
اولاد مايكل وافقت أيضًا على الشراكة معي.
I won't go into the details, but yes...
لن أخوض في ذلك التفاصيل لكن نعم...
they agreed.
اتفقوا.
Oh... [CHUCKLES] That's really good.
أوه... [ضحكة مكتومة] هذا جيد حقا.
You know, this is what I really wanted. I just...
كما تعلمون، هذا هو ما أردت حقا. أنا فقط...
I just didn't think it would be this easy.
أنا فقط لم أفكر سيكون الأمر بهذه السهولة.
[LUNA CHUCKLES]
[ضحكة لونا]
Here are our terms.
وهنا شروطنا.
Our lawyers have reviewed them.
وقد قام محامونا بمراجعتها.
Good.
جيد.
I'll have our lawyer review this, too.
سآخذ محامينا مراجعة هذا أيضا.
But if it were up to me, I'd approve it right away.
لكن لو كان الأمر بيدي سأوافق عليه على الفور.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[ضحكة مكتومة بهدوء]
Good.
جيد.
I'm very excited to be working with you.
أنا متحمس جدا للعمل معك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
[MARINA] Juan!
[مارينا] خوان!
Juan!
خوان!
Ma'am?
سيدتي؟
I didn't realize it was you, ma'am.
لم أكن أدرك أنه أنت، سيدتي.
I've been trying to get your attention.
لقد كنت أحاول لجذب انتباهك.
I have news about your father.
لدي أخبار عن والدك
Really, ma'am?
حقا يا سيدتي؟
Someone spotted him in the town of Dagat-Dagatan.
شخص ما رصده في مدينة داجات داجاتان.
Dagat-Dagatan?
داجات داجاتان؟
He's never mentioned that place to me.
لم يذكر قط هذا المكان لي.
But it's a credible lead.
لكنها قيادة موثوقة.
According to the report,
بحسب التقرير
your father had a project there.
والدك كان لديه مشروع هناك.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Can I get the contact information
هل يمكنني الحصول على معلومات الاتصال
of the person who reported that?
الشخص من أبلغ بذلك؟
It's back at the station.
لقد عاد إلى المحطة.
I'll just send it to you.
سأرسلها لك فقط.
Okay, ma'am. Thank you very much.
حسنا سيدتي. شكراً جزيلاً.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل الموسيقى المثيرة]
You apologize to the people you hurt
أنت تعتذر للأشخاص الذين تؤذيهم
because you're considerate of their feelings.
لأنك متفهم بمشاعرهم.
But here you are,
ولكن ها أنت ذا،
apologizing for selfish reasons.
الاعتذار لأسباب أنانية.
- Justin! - Go away!
- جوستين! - إرحل!
Go back to the hotel.
العودة إلى الفندق.
Justin!
جاستن!
Wait a minute, Justin!
انتظر لحظة يا جاستن!
Do you know Peter Montevilla?
هل تعلم بيتر مونتيفيلا؟
He's madly in love with Solenn.
إنه واقع في الحب بجنون مع سولين.
The map that leads to the treasure hidden in Hotel 88.
الخريطة التي تؤدي إلى الكنز المخبأ في فندق 88.
- [VASE SHATTERS] - [SHOUTS]
- [تحطم المزهرية] - [صيحات]